Register of the William T. Poole collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Un-American Activities Subject File, 1920-1976 (Box 51-231.)
  - Lens, Sidney. Journal articles, clippings, Congressional speech and hearing testimony, American Security Council dossier, and HUAC dossier, 1962-1969 (Folder 117: 23)
  - Liberated Church Press [Berkeley]. Serial issues and directory, 1969 (Folder 118: 1)
  - Liberated Guardian. Circular letter and serial issues, 1970-1971 (Folder 118: 2)
  - Liberation (Folder 118)
    - General. Circulars, clippings, and printed articles from the journal, 1966-1972 (Folder 118: 3)
    - Serial issues (Folder 118)
      - 1962-1965 (Folder 118: 4)
      - 1966-1967 (Folder 118: 5)
      - 1968-1972 (Folder 118: 6)
  - Liberation News Service (Folder 118)
    - General. Letter, circulars, leaflets, flyers, and clippings, 1969-1972 (Folder 118: 7)
    - Serial issuances. Photocopies in many cases (Folder 118)
      - 1969 January (Folder 118: 8)
      - 1969 June (Folder 118: 9)
      - 1969 July (Folder 118: 10)
      - 1969 August (Folder 118: 11)
      - 1969 September (Folder 119: 1)
      - 1969 October (Folder 119: 2-3)
      - 1969 November (Folder 119: 4)
      - 1969 November (contd.) (Folder 120: 1)
      - 1969 December (Folder 120: 2-3)
      - 1970 January (Folder 120: 4)
      - 1970 January (contd.) (Folder 121: 1-2)
      - 1970 February (Folder 121: 3-4)
      - 1970 March (Folder 121: 5)
      - 1970 March (contd.) (Folder 122: 1)
      - 1970 April (Folder 122: 2-4)
      - 1970 May (Folder 122: 5)
      - 1970 May (contd.) (Folder 123: 1-2)
      - 1970 June (Folder 123: 3-4)
      - 1970 July (Folder 124: 1-3)
      - 1970 August (Folder 124: 4-5)
      - 1970 September (Folder 124: 6)
      - 1971 April (Folder 125: 1-2)
      - 1971 May (Folder 125: 3)
      - 1972 March (Folder 125: 4)
  - Liberator. Serial issues and HUAC memoranda, 1962-1967 (Folder 125: 5)
  - Liberty Book Club. Circular and serial issue (Promethean Review), 1955-1959 (Folder 125: 6)
  - Link: The Serviceman's Link to Peace [re GI dissidents]. Press releases, flyers, leaflets, and circulars, 1969 (Folder 126: 1)
  - Lisker, Roy. Clipping and HUAC memorandum, 1965-1966 (Folder 126: 2)
  - Lobby of Americans [re Vietnam War]. Press releases, leaflets, flyers, and circulars, 1971 (Folder 126: 3)
  - Lomax, Louis. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 126: 4)
  - Long March [Baltimore]. Serial issue, 1966 (Folder 126: 5)
  - Long March Movement Center [Los Angeles]. Bulletins, circulars, and flyers, 1972-1974 (Folder 126: 6)
  - Lonidier, Fred. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 126: 7)
  - Los Angeles Citizens for an Honorable Non-Violent U.S. Vietnam Policy. Printed appeals, 1965 (Folder 126: 8)
  - Los Angeles Committee for Defense of the Bill of Rights. Press releases, circulars, and programs, 1966-1970 (Folder 126: 9)
  - Los Angeles Committee for Defense of the Bill of Rights and the Protection of the Foreign Born. Press releases and circulars, 1965-1966 (Folder 126: 10)
  - Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born (Folder 126)
    - Correspondence. Includes circular letters (Folder 126)
      - 1951-1953 (Folder 126: 11)
      - 1954-1956 (Folder 126: 12)
      - 1958-1959 (Folder 126: 13)
      - 1960-1961 (Folder 126: 14)
      - Undated (Folder 126: 15)
    - Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born issuances. Leaflets, flyers, circulars, minutes, conference proceedings, resolutions, reports, petitions, press releases, and programs (Folder 127)
      - 1950-1951 (Folder 127: 1)
      - 1952 (Folder 127: 2)
      - 1953 (Folder 127: 3)
      - 1954 (Folder 127: 4)
      - 1955 (Folder 127: 5)
      - 1956 (Folder 127: 6)
      - 1958 (Folder 127: 7)
      - 1959 (Folder 127: 8)
      - (Folder 127)
      - 1960 (Folder 128: 1)
      - 1961 (Folder 128: 2)
      - 1965 (Folder 128: 3)
      - Undated (Folder 128: 4)
    - Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born publications (Folder 128)
      - Torch. Serial issues, 1951-1954 (Folder 128: 5)
      - Torchlight. Serial issues, 1954-1965 (Folder 128: 6)
      - Pamphlets (For a People's Lobby; Shame of a Nation; Victims of the Walter-McCarran Law and How They Are Defended), 1954-1955 (Folder 128: 7)
    - Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born internal documents. Drafts of letters and writings, working materials, and notes. Some similar unidentified materials filed under Immigration (General) may also be from Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born files (Folder 128)
      - 1954-1958 (Folder 128: 8)
      - 1959 (Folder 128: 9)
      - 1960 (Folder 129: 1)
      - 1961 (Folder 129: 2)
      - Undated (Folder 129: 3)
    - Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born financial records. Canceled checks, receipts, and financial summaries, 1953-1959 (Folder 129: 4)
    - Fifth Annual Southern California Conference to Protect the Rights of Foreign Born Americans registration cards (Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born event), 1955 (Folder 129: 5)
    - Fifth Annual Southern California Conference to Protect the Rights of Foreign Born Americans registration cards (contd.) (Folder 130: 1-2)
    - Material about the Los Angeles Committee for Protection of Foreign Born. Informants' reports and HUAC memoranda, 1953-1960 (Folder 130: 3)
  - Los Angeles Institute of Marxist Studies. Flyers, ca. 1973-1974 (Folder 130: 4)
  - Louise Pettibone Smith Birthday Committee. Testimonial dinner souvenir pamphlet, 1962 (Folder 130: 5)
  - Lovestone, Jay, and Rea S. Van Fossen. Related clippings, 1955 (Folder 130: 6)
  - Lovett, Robert Morss. Letters, journal articles, clippings, and letterhead data, 1935-1940 (Folder 130: 7)
  - Lower Eastside Mobilization for Peace Action [New York City]. Printed appeals, clipping, and informant's report, 1967-1968 (Folder 130: 8)
  - Luftig vs. McNamara Committee [re Vietnam War]. Printed appeal, 1966 (Folder 130: 9)
  - Lynd, Staughton. Letter and clippings, 1965-1967 (Folder 130: 10)
  - Lynn, Conrad. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 130: 11)
  - McCarthy, Eugene J. Circular letter and invitation, 1971 (Folder 131: 1)
  - McCloskey, Paul N., Jr. Circular letters, press releases, and bill introduced, 1971 (Folder 131: 2)
  - McGovern, George S. Circular letters, printed speeches, and printed appeal, 1958-1972 (Folder 131: 3)
  - McReynolds, David. Printed letter to the editor, and HUAC memorandum, 1966-1967 (Folder 131: 4)
  - Madison Citizens for a Vote on Vietnam [Madison, Wisconsin]. Leaflets, circulars, printed articles, letters, HUAC memoranda, draft speech for Congressman Edwin Willis, and photocopies of index card files, 1961-1968 (Folder 131: 5)
  - Mainstream. Serial issues and printed article from the journal, 1947-1956 (Folder 131: 6)
  - Majority Report. Serial issues, 1971 (Folder 131: 7)
  - Mandel, David. Printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 131: 8)
  - Mandel, William M. Letter and printed articles, 1965 (Folder 131: 9)
  - Marc Blitzstein Memorial Concert (New York City, 1964). Printed announcement (Folder 131: 10)
  - March of Labor. Serial issues, 1949-1956 (Folder 131: 11)
  - March 25th Peace Committee [Chicago]. Leaflets, 1967 (Folder 131: 12)
  - March 26th Arrangement Committee [re Vietnam War; Chicago]. Leaflets and clippings, 1966 (Folder 131: 13)
  - Marian Davis Scholarship Fund. Circular letters and leaflets, 1966-1969 (Folder 131: 14)
  - Martin Sostre Defense Committee. Circulars, flyers, leaflets, clippings, printed articles, and pamphlets (Letters from Prison; Martin Sostre in Court), 1967-1969 (Folder 132: 1)
  - Mary Washington College antiwar protests. Printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 132: 2)
  - Maryland Freedom Union. Clippings, 1966-1967 (Folder 132: 3)
  - Maryland Socialist League. Constitution and flyer, 1966 (Folder 132: 4)
  - Marzani and Munsell, Publishers. Includes Prometheus Paperbacks. Circulars, catalogs, brochure for Eugene J. McCarthy for President, and pamphlet (Journey to the Soviet Trade Unions), 1962-1968 (Folder 132: 5)
  - Massachusetts Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee. Letters, circulars, Congressional speech, petitions, and lists of endorsers, 1966-1968 (Folder 132: 6)
  - Massachusetts Council of American-Soviet Friendship. Clipping, 1943 (Folder 132: 7)
  - Massachusetts Political Action for Peace. Leaflet, 1967 (Folder 132: 8)
  - Masses and Mainstream. Serial issues and printed article from the journal (Folder 132)
    - 1948 (Folder 132: 9-10)
    - 1949 (Folder 133: 1)
    - 1950 (Folder 133: 2-3)
    - 1951 (Folder 133: 4)
    - 1952 (Folder 133: 5)
    - 1953 (Folder 134: 1)
    - 1954 (Folder 134: 2)
    - 1955 (Folder 134: 3)
  - Mau Mau Society [New York City]. HUAC memorandum, ca. 1967 (Folder 134: 4)
  - May 2nd Movement [originally May 2nd Committee]. Letters, circulars, leaflets, flyers, clippings, journal articles, bulletins, press releases, statements, pamphlet (Twenty Years in Jail for Traveling to Cuba!), serial issues (Free Student), and HUAC memoranda and speeches, 1964-1966 (Folder 134: 5)
  - Mayday Collective (Folder 134)
    - General. Circulars, leaflets, flyers, and clippings, 1969-1971 (Folder 134: 6)
    - Serial issues (Mayday; Hard Times), 1968-1971 (Folder 135: 1)
  - Medical Aid Committee for Vietnam. Correspondence (including with International Red Cross), circulars, printed appeals, clippings, journal articles, and HUAC memoranda, 1965-1966 (Folder 135: 2)
  - Medical Aid for Indochina. Circulars, leaflets, flyers, and press releases, 1972-1973 (Folder 135: 3)
  - Medical Committee for Human Rights. Circulars, leaflets, flyers, press releases, clippings, journal articles, and serial issues (Health Liberation News; Health Rights News), 1967-1973 (Folder 135: 4)
  - Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Library [Berkeley]. Serial publication (Civil Liberties Docket), 1969 (Folder 135: 5)
  - Melish, John Howard. Amicae curiae brief in case of John Howard Melish et al. vs. Church of the Holy Trinity before U.S. Supreme Court, 1950 (Folder 135: 6)
  - Mellen, James. Clippings, 1965 (Folder 135: 7)
  - Members of Congress for Peace through Law. Press releases, circular letters to other members of Congress, reports, clippings, and Congressional speeches, 1969-1974 (Folder 135: 8)
  - Messages for Peace [Roosevelt, New Jersey]. Printed appeal, 1967 (Folder 135: 9)
  - Methodist Federation for Social Action (Folder 135)
    - Correspondence, 1935-1970. (Folder 135: 10)
    - Methodist Federation for Social Action issuances (Folder 136)
      - General. Annual meeting agenda and reports, circulars, resolutions, speeches, newsletters, letterhead data, and pamphlet (The Harry F. Ward Sampler), 1928-1968 (Folder 136: 1)
    - Social Service Bulletin. Serial issues and printed articles from the journal (Folder 136)
      - 1920-1923 (Folder 136: 2)
      - 1924-1927 (Folder 136: 3)
      - 1928-1931 (Folder 136: 4)
      - 1932-1935 (Folder 137: 1)
    - Social Questions Bulletin. Serial issues and printed articles from the journal (Folder 137)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 137: 2)
      - 1941-1944 (Folder 137: 3)
      - 1950-1959 (Folder 137: 4)
      - 1960-1961 (Folder 137: 5)
      - 1962-1963 (Folder 137: 6)
      - (Folder 137)
      - 1964-1965 (Folder 138: 1)
      - 1966-1967 (Folder 138: 2)
      - 1968-1971 (Folder 138: 3)
    - Material about the Methodist Federation for Social Action. Letter, memorandum, printed articles, and pamphlets (Information concerning the Methodist Federation for Social Action; Is There a Pink Fringe in the Methodist Church?), 1950-1956 (Folder 138: 4)
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing [New York City]. Flyers, newsletter, and pamphlet (Your Home Is Your Hassle), 1964-1971 (Folder 138: 5)
  - Metropolitan Music School [New York City]. Schedules and HUAC memoranda, 1954-1966 (Folder 138: 6)
  - Mezey, Robert. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 138: 7)
  - Miami Peace Center [Coral Gables, Florida]. Clippings, 1966 (Folder 138: 8)
  - Michael Gold Memorial Committee. Printed announcements, 1967 (Folder 138: 9)
  - Michigan Committee for Protection of Foreign Born. Press releases, circulars, flyers, leaflets, and newsletters (Defender), 1950-1956oHH (Folder 138: 10)
  - Mid-Atlantic Committee on Fort Detrick. Flyer, 1969 (Folder 138: 11)
  - Middle East (General). Flyers, leaflets, printed appeals, press releases, serial issues (Committee to Support Middle East Liberation Newsletter; Communist Party of Israel Information Bulletin; Palestine Digest), and pamphlet (Why Do We Support the PFLP?), issued by miscellaneous groups, re solidarity with Palestinians and other peoples of the Middle East, 1955-1973 (Folder 138: 12)
  - Middle East Report. Photocopy of the journal's mailing list, undated (Folder 138: 13)
  - Midwest Committee for Protection of Foreign Born. Conference reports, press releases, circulars, and leaflets, 1951-1959 (Folder 139: 1)
  - Midwest Conference for a Relevant Social Science (Chicago, 1973). Letter, program, and conference materials (Folder 139: 2)
  - Midwest Faculty Committee on Vietnam. Flyer, 1966 (Folder 139: 3)
  - Miller, Arthur. Clippings and letterhead data, 1947-1951 (Folder 139: 4)
  - Miller, David John. Clippings and HUAC memorandum, 1965-1969 (Folder 139: 5)
  - Milwaukee 14 Defense Committee. Circular letter and leaflet, 1969 (Folder 139: 6)
  - Minnesota Committee for Protection of Foreign Born. Press release and bulletins, 1959 (Folder 139: 7)
  - Minnesota Committee to End the War in Vietnam. Circular letter and newsletters (Crisis), 1966 (Folder 139: 8)
  - Minority of One (Folder 139)
    - General. Circulars and printed articles, 1965-1968 (Folder 139: 9)
    - Serial issues (Folder 139)
      - 1961-1963 (Folder 139: 10)
      - 1964 (Folder 139: 11)
      - 1965-1966 (Folder 139: 12)
      - 1967-1968 (Folder 139: 13)
  - Minutemen. Includes Committee to Free the Korean War Prisoners (Folder 140)
    - Minutemen issuances (Folder 140)
      - General. Leaflets and flyers, 1961-1966 (Folder 140: 1)
      - Internal documents. Bulletins, training directives, membership applications, and letter to John F. Kennedy, 1961-1967 (Folder 140: 2)
      - On Target. Serial issues, 1963-1965 (Folder 140: 3)
      - Pamphlets (The Minutemen: America's Last Line of Defence against Communism; Principles of Guerrilla Warfare), 1961-1962 (Folder 140: 4)
    - Material about the Minutemen (Folder 140)
      - General. Letters, notes, Federal Bureau of Investigation wanted notices, and miscellany, 1965-1968 (Folder 140: 5)
      - Clippings and printed articles, 1961-1968 (Folder 140: 6-7)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party. Flyers, clippings, and internal proposal document, 1965-1967 (Folder 141: 1)
  - Mitchell, David Henry, III. Flyers, clippings, and HUAC memorandum, 1965-1968 (Folder 141: 2)
  - Mitchell, Parren J. Press release, 1971 (Folder 141: 3)
  - Mitford, Jessica. Pamphlets (Jessica Mitford and the Red Death; Legal Aspects of the Mitford-Treuhaft Case), 1965 (Folder 141: 4)
  - Mobilization for Democracy [Los Angeles]. Letters, 1946 (Folder 141: 5)
  - Monroe Defense Committee [re Monroe, North Carolina, black defendants]. Circulars, leaflets, flyers, and pamphlet (Letters from Prison), 1961-1965 (Folder 141: 6)
  - Monthly Review. Circulars, catalog, and Leo Huberman memorial service pamphlet, 1966-1968 (Folder 141: 7)
  - Mooney, Tom. Pamphlet (Tom Mooney Betrayed by Labor Leaders), 1931 (Folder 141: 8)
  - Morehouse College antiwar protests. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 141: 9)
  - Morning Freiheit Association. Clipping, letterhead data, serial issues (Jewish Life), and pamphlet (The Jewish People Face the Postwar World), 1945-1972 (Folder 141: 10)
  - Morrison, Norman R. Clipping, 1965 (Folder 141: 11)
  - Mothers' Defense Committee [re New York City black defendants]. HUAC memoranda, 1967 (Folder 141: 12)
  - Movement for a Free Philippines. Printed issuances, 1973 (Folder 141: 13)
  - Movement for a New Congress. Booklet (Vote Power: The Official Activist Campaigner's Handbook), 1970 (Folder 141: 14)
  - Moving the Movement Fund. Circulars, 1969 (Folder 141: 15)
  - Music and Art Students against the War in Vietnam. Flyer, 1967 (Folder 141: 16)
  - Musicians Congress Committee. Brochure, ca. 1940s (Folder 141: 17)
  - Muste, A. J. Clippings, 1967 (Folder 141: 18)
  - Nagasaki Day Memorial (Washington, D.C., 1969). Flyer (Folder 141: 19)
  - Nashville Committee for Alternatives to War in Vietnam. Serial issues (Confrontation), 1966 (Folder 141: 20)
  - Nation. Circular, serial issues, and printed articles from the journal, 1950-1971 (Folder 141: 21)
  - Nation of Islam. Flyers, circular, clippings, journal articles, serial issue (Muhammad Speaks), and HUAC memoranda, 1960-1974 (Folder 142: 1)
  - National Action/Research on the Military Industrial Complex [American Friends Service Committee project]. Flyers and circulars, 1969-1973 (Folder 142: 2)
  - National Alliance against Racist and Political Repression. (Folder 142)
    See also National Defense Organization against Racist and Political Repression Founding Conference (Chicago, 1973)
    - General. Minutes, conference proceedings, resolutions, statement, flyers, circulars, and list of officers, 1973-1974 (Folder 142: 3)
    - National Alliance against Racist and Political Repression publications. Serial issues (Organizer), and pamphlet (North Carolina: Laboratory for Racism and Repression), 1974 (Folder 142: 4)
  - National Anti-Imperialist Conference in Solidarity with African Liberation (Chicago, 1973) (Folder 142)
    - General. Conference proceedings and documents, resolutions, press releases, flyers, circulars, serial issues (African Agenda), and HISC memoranda, 1973 (Folder 142: 5)
    - United Nations bulletins re South African apartheid circulated at the conference, 1972-1973 (Folder 142: 6)
  - National Artists' Protest [re Vietnam War]. Clipping, 1967 (Folder 142: 7)
  - National Assembly for Democratic Rights (New York City, 1961). Conference proceedings, circular letters, leaflet, and clipping, 1961-1962 (Folder 142: 8)
  - National Association for Irish Freedom. Circular letter, leaflet, flyer, serial issue (Saoirse Freedom), and pamphlet (Massacre at Derry), 1971-1972 (Folder 142: 9)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People. Circular letters, flyer, leaflet, and pamphlet (The Ugly Truth about the NAACP), 1953-1971 (Folder 142: 10)
  - National Association of Social Workers. Printed appeal re Vietnam War, 1967 (Folder 142: 11)
  - National Black Anti-War and Anti-Draft Union. Printed article and HUAC memoranda, 1968 (Folder 143: 1)
  - National Campaign to Impeach Nixon [Richard M. Nixon]. Letter, press releases, circulars, flyers, list of sponsors, printed article, serial issues (National Impeachment News), stickers and memorabilia, booklet ("Bribery, and Other High Crimes and Misdemeanors": The Offenses of Richard M. Nixon: A Lawyer's Guide for the People of the United States), and Congressional memorandum re impeachment proceedings against Richard M. Nixon, 1973-1974 (Folder 143: 2)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees. Flyers, circulars, serial issues (New Solidarity), and pamphlet (Scrapping the War Machine), 1968-1974 (Folder 143: 3)
  - National Citizens' Committee to Defend Academic Freedom at St. John's University. Printed appeals, 1966 (Folder 143: 4)
  - National Citizens' Lobby. Flyer, 1969 (Folder 143: 5)
  - National Citizens Political Action Committee. Correspondence, leaflets, circulars, flyers, newsletters, printed articles, clippings, lists of sponsors, and financial records, 1944-1946 (Folder 143: 6)
  - National Coalition against War, Racism and Repression. Conference proceedings (Chicago, 1971), list of participants, circulars, flyers, and newsletter, 1970-1971 (Folder 143: 7)
  - National Coalition to Fight Inflation and Unemployment. Circulars, ca. 1974 (Folder 143: 8)
  - National Committee against Repressive Legislation. Letter, circulars, flyers, leaflets, other printed matter, and HISC statement, 1972-1974 (Folder 143: 9)
  - National Committee for a Citizens' Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes in Vietnam. Press release and report, 1970 (Folder 143: 10)
  - National Committee for a Political Settlement in Vietnam. Clipping, 1968 (Folder 143: 11)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy [SANE] (Folder 143)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1969. (Folder 143: 12)
    - SANE issuances (Folder 144)
      - General. Press releases, printed appeals, leaflets, flyers, circulars, and reprints of Congressional testimony and journal articles, 1958-1973 (Folder 144: 1-3)
      - SANE Report. Printed issuances, 1969-1973 (Folder 144: 4)
    - Material about SANE. Clippings, journal articles, and W. E. B. DuBois Club memoranda, 1965-1968 (Folder 145: 1)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress. Circular letters, 1970-1974 (Folder 145: 2)
  - National Committee for Free Elections in Sunflower County [Mississippi]. Circular letter, 1966 (Folder 145: 3)
  - National Committee for the Albany Defendants [Albany, Georgia]. Petition and pamphlet (The Albany Cases), 1966 (Folder 145: 4)
  - National Committee of Inquiry [re civil rights for blacks]. Clipping, 1968 (Folder 145: 5)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee (Folder 145)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1969. (Folder 145: 6)
    - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee issuances (Folder 145)
      - General. Press releases, petitions, circulars, leaflets, flyers, printed appeals, and reprints, 1959-1970 (Folder 145: 7-8)
      - Bulletins and newsletters (Abolition News), 1964-1971 (Folder 145: 9)
      - Pamphlets (Folder 145)
        - A Collection of Editorials and Resolutions in Opposition to the Un-American Activities Committee [2 editions], 1960-1962 (Folder 145: 10)
        - Dialogue on the Constitutionality of the Committee on Un-American Activities; The 89th Congress and the Abolition of HUAC; House Un-American Activities Committee: Bulwark of Segregation, 1965 (Folder 146: 1)
    - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee internal documents. Minutes, agenda, reports, and financial records, 1960-1969 (Folder 146: 2)
    - Material about the National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee. Journal articles, Congressional speeches, and HUAC press releases, reports, notes, and memoranda, 1960-1969 (Folder 146: 3)
  - National Committee to Defeat the Mundt Bill [predecessor of Internal Security Act (McCarran Act)]. HUAC report, 1950 (Folder 146: 4)
  - National Committee to Defend the Civil Liberties of the Anti-War Movement. Clipping, 1966 (Folder 146: 5)
  - National Committee to Repeal the McCarran Act. Letters, circulars, petition, printed appeals, memoranda, flyers, and pamphlet (What You Need to Know about the McCarran Act), 1951-1966 (Folder 146: 6)
  - National Committee to Secure Justice in the Rosenberg Case [re Julius and Ethel Rosenberg]. (Folder 146: 7)
    Includes subsequent National Committee to Re-open the Rosenberg Case. Letter, press releases, flyers, financial records, clippings, and printed articles, 1952-1975
  - National Committee to Win the Peace. Letter, Howard K. Smith radio broadcast transcript, and pamphlet (Open Secret: Reports on the Betrayal of Roosevelt's Peace Policy and American Preparations for World War III), 1946 (Folder 146: 8)
  - National Conference for New Politics (Folder 147)
    - General. Letters, printed appeals, circulars, clippings, printed articles, serial issues (New Politics News), and report, 1966-1968 (Folder 147: 1)
    - National Conference for New Politics internal documents re the National Convention for New Politics (Chicago, 1967). Photocopies (Folder 147)
      - Correspondence, principally with other liberal and leftist organization re participation in the Convention, 1967 (Folder 147: 2)